To run the app:
1. Make sure, that Python 3.6 and Django 1.11 are installed on your machine.
2. Clone the following GitHub repo:
https://github.com/tatankayotanka/mysite
3. In your favourite shell, change into the outer mysite directory of the cloned repo.
4. In the shell, run the following command:
python manage.py runserver
5. In your favourite browser, open the following link:
http://127.0.0.1:8000/task/
6. Click <Register> in the navigation bar, to create an account and start working.
